

# Moetaz doghman

Computer Engineering Student

moetaz.doghman@esprit.tn 📞 52464649 💡 Bizerte,Tunisia

https://github.com/Moetaz-doghman

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/moetaz-doghman-409aa8213/

### **Profile**

Third-year student in the Computer Engineering program at the Private Higher School of Engineering and Technologies - ESPRIT. Creative web developer with 4 years of programming expertise. Fast learner who excels at problem solving and developing innovative ideas for website solutions, as well as a strong ability to communicate ideas clearly.

#### **Education**

**Engineering cycle (software engineering),** The Private Higher School of Engineering and Technology (ESPRIT)

2019 - present | Tunis ghazela, Tunisia

Bachelor's degree (science), Farhat Hached High School

2015 - 2019 | BIZERTE, Tunisia

## **Projects**

Projet Pi (GiveBack)

2023 DEMO ☑

Development of a social media-inspired web platform to facilitate collaboration in the realm of volunteering and nonprofit organizations, as part of an academic project.

Technologies used: MERN stack

Web Project (Kadem)

2023

Development of a web application for student contract management.

Technologies used: Angular for the frontend and Spring Boot for the backend.

#### PIDEV integration project (TechShop)

2022

Development of a Symfony e-commerce website.

Creating a CodeName One Mobile App(Consumption of APIs made on the Symfony part).

Creation of a Desktop application with JavaFX.

# Web Project (Nature Pet)

2021

Nature Pet is a dynamic e-commerce website powered by PHP, providing a convenient and reliable platform for pet enthusiasts to find a wide variety of animals and accessories.

## **Professional Experience**

## **Summer internship**

06.2023 - 08.2023 | Bizerte, Tunisia

Full-stack web developer, infoPLUS ☑

DEMO ☑

During this internship, I contributed to the development of a full-stack web site for INFOplus. Using the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js), I designed and implemented the essential features of the site to meet the needs of the company.

**Summer internship** 

08.2022 - 09.2022 | Ghazela, Tunisia

Web Developer, ESPRIT ☑

Development of the ESPRIT Career Center Website

**Summer internship** 

07.2021 - 09.2021 | BIZERTE, Tunisia

Symfony Developer, Tunisian Smart Cities 🗷

As an intern Symfony developer at Tunisian Smart Cities, I worked on the "Ma ville en Poche" project, a web application aimed at connecting the city of Bizerte and providing citizens with real-time access to all essential services.

# **Skills**

• C, C++, C#

Mern stack

- Java,Framework Spring
- Angular

- Html,Css,Boostrap
- Others : Git, Uml, Trello, Jira
- Python,Framework Django

# Languages

Arabic

• • • •

English

. . . . .

French